'use strict';

const STORE = [

    // Question 1
  {
    question: 'Making someone feel _____ is the best way to improve their mood.',
    answers: [
      'Valued',
      'Attractive',
      'Flattered',
      'Powerful'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Valued'
  },

    // Question 2
  {
    question: 'Where is the best place to stand at a networking event?',
    answers: [
      'Near the entrance to the event',
      'At the food table so you can sit with people',
      'Where people exit the bar',
      'Next to someone you know'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Where people exit the bar'
  },

    // Question 3
  {
    question: 'Which of these habits tend to annoy people the most?',
    answers: [
      'People who are too talkative',
      'People who are too quiet',
      'People who show off',
      'People who are fake'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'People who are fake'
  },

    // Question 4
  {
    question: 'Which saying about people is most true?',
    answers: [
      '“Opposites attract.”',
      '“Birds of a feather flock together.”',
      '“One bad apple spoils the bunch.”',
      '“Never bite the hand that feeds you.”'
    ],
    correctAnswer: '“Birds of a feather flock together.”'
  },

    // Question 5
  {
    question: 'How much of your personality comes from our genes?',
    answers: [
      'Very little. Our personality is mostly formed by how we are raised.',
      '35 percent to 50 percent',
      '55 percent to 75 percent',
      'A lot. Our personality is mostly formed by our genetics and DNA.'
    ],
    correctAnswer: '35 percent to 50 percent'
  },

    // Question 6
  {
    question: 'People will pay more for something that:',
    answers: [
      'Their friends have also bought',
      'A doctor recommends',
      'Matches their personality',
      'They customized'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'They customized'
  },

    // Question 7
  {
    question: 'In the average conversation, people typically hold eye contact what percent of the time in a conversation?',
    answers: [
      '31 percent',
      '51 percent',
      '61 percent',
      '91 percent'
    ],
    correctAnswer: '61 percent'
  },

    // Question 8
  {
    question: 'The best way to get someone on the same page as you is to:',
    answers: [
      'Tell them a story',
      'Pay them a compliment',
      'Make them laugh',
      'Say something surprising'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Tell them a story'
  },

    // Question 9
  {
    question: 'Our brains are the most active when we are chatting about:',
    answers: [
      'Our crush',
      'The latest juicy gossip',
      'Ourselves',
      'The latest thriller'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Ourselves'
  },

    // Question 10
  {
    question: 'When you first meet someone, you are LEAST likely to be able to accurately guess:',
    answers: [
      'How extroverted they are',
      'How much they worry',
      'Their IQ',
      'How organized they are'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'How much they worry'
  }
];
